Hampus Isebring

0763-117617

hampus.isebring@medieinstitutet.se

Halmstad



Portfolio page







About me

My hope is that my skills in digital design, particularly UX | UI and service design combined with my newly enhanced skills in front end development can contribute to a broad understanding of how the creation of new digital solutions from start to delivery is done.

As a person I value teamwork and working together towards a goal. To me, it does not matter who comes up with an idea or whether the team proceeds further with it or not. In that regard I am prestigeless and I look at it as a team effort. In the projects I have participated during my studies, both at Halmstad University and Medieinstitutet, every project has been done in a team and we have supplemented and inspired each other, which in my opinion is a strength.

My practical experience prior to my entry into digital design and coding has been in areas such as service and preschool. During these jobs I gathered much experience in collaboration, problem solving and patience. The reason I mention patience is due to certain situations in service and preschool that affected me psychologically. Some of these situations truly tested my patience, and I learned a lot from them.

1



I have a big collection of Pokémon cards, both from childhood and newer sets.

(\$-\$) 2

I am into gaming and got a fondness for Nintendo due to growing up with N64 and SNES.

TV

3

I am playing the guitar and recently learned the intro song to the 90's classic series Twin Peaks.



I love many different genres of music and got a collection of vinyl records and a record player.



I adopted a polar bear via WWF in 2018 and still support the polar bears.



I am a big fan of Tolkien and got the quote "Not All Those . Who Wander Are Lost" tattooed on my

(**) Accessibility I strive to do inclusive design. I am a big

believer of the curb-cut effect. In short, when we design for disabilities, we make things better for everyone. One of my favorite examples of this is the SMS function.

Work Experience

02

03

04

05

Snabbaross Halmstad. 2022. June-August.

Seasonal job. I worked at the dairy and charcuterie department, where I for example unpacked the daily arrival of goods. Furthermore me and my coworkers made sure the department was good looking and assisted our customers. I also worked at the checkout.

SIZCILINI OUTLET Halmstad. 2019. 2 months.

Temporary post. I unpacked arriving goods, assisted customers, had a close collaboration with my coworkers, and made sure the store was good looking. Furthermore I worked at the checkout.



Halmstad Halmstad. 2017-2018.

Monthly employment. During my work in this preschool my main assignment and focus was to do activities and be a helping hand for the children. I really appreciate how much I learned about different personalities during this period of time. Though some days and parts could be challenging psychologically, in the end I turned out to be a more experienced and developed human being.

HEMMAKVÄLL Halmstad. 2015-2016.

Hourly employment. During my time at Hemmakväll I

learned the foundation of how to work in a store. First and foremost, I learned how to tag movies and other goods. Furthermore I learned how to assist customers at the checkout, and since one of Hemmakvälls main focuses are bulk confectionery, I learned how to handle bulk confectionery properly. My favorite part was assisting and talking to customers.

Halmstad Halmstad. 2014.

Temporary post. During my work as administrator at Halmstad Kommun I assisted with several office assignments. One example is Sommarkraft, which is a project directed towards first year high school students. There they can apply to different seasonal jobs provided by Halmstad kommun. My part was registrering these seasonal jobs and matching appliers and jobs.

Education



2022-09-13 - ongoing - Front End Developer. Vocational University. Medieinstitutet Gothenburg.

This education covers the fundamentals of front end development such as HTML, CSS and JavaScript. We also learn TypeScript and libraries such as Bootstrap and React.js. This education combines theoretical and practical learning.

2022-01 - 2022-03 - Individual course Social Sustainability. Halmstad University. Individual course in the subject Social sustainability. An introduction to the three dimensions of

sustainable development: Economic, Environment and Social sustainability.

2019-09 - 2022-06 - Digital Design and Innovation. Halmstad University. 180 hp Bachelor degree program with an introduction to the work as a digital

designer. I have learned the foundations of how to work as a UX | UI, Interaction and Service designer. It has combined both theorertical and practical work.

2014-2015- Sale & Customer service directed towards retail. Astar Halmstad. This education specified in teaching sale techniques and customer service. I chose the direction retail

hence my interest to work in a store. One important part I learned here is how people can be categorized as different colors: red, blue, green and yellow and it's our job to identify and treat them properly thereafter.



STAR

2010-08-2013-06 - Aesthetics with Specialisation Drama. Sturegymnasiet Halmstad. An incredible journey for me personally. By standing on stage I got to know myself better and challenge

myself constantly. This period of my life is something I will carry on and remember throughout the years as a time where I developed as a human.





Languages

- Fluent

- Native

Front End Developer Student

Halmstad, Sweden